A belated birthday present.
一份迟到的生日礼物
Turned 24 years old yesterday.
她昨天刚满24岁
And Zheng Qinwen in front of her home crowd
郑钦文在主场观众面前
into the semifinals of the China Open.
打进了中国网球公开赛半决赛
Six three, seven six.
比分6比3 7比6
What a win. What a moment.
多么精彩的胜利 多么动人的时刻
Second time that she's been
这是她第二次
in the semifinals here in Beijing.
打进北京站半决赛
北京时间10月9号下午
中网1/4决赛
24岁生日刚过
郑钦文对上世界第7 斯维托丽娜
首盘 郑钦文先破发 拿到2比0
4比2时 她又兑现第五个破发点
5比2发球拿盘没成
下一局 她再拿到盘点
Finds the line.
压线得分
Good set of tennis from Zheng Qinwen.
郑钦文这一盘打得很好
Coach likes it.
教练很满意
Crowd is loving it,
现场观众也看得过瘾
as Zheng Qinwen from China
中国选手郑钦文
playing well in front of her home crowd.
在主场观众面前表现出色
Looking to get to a second semifinal in Beijing.
她争取第二次打进北京站半决赛
She's halfway there. Six three.
现在已走过一半 首盘6比3
第二盘3比3 郑钦文的发球局失守
她在下一局 用正手压向底线角落
又拿到破发机会
Great forehand into the corner,
漂亮的正手 直入底线角落
and a big roar from...
还有一声响亮的大吼
这个破发点
郑钦文随后兑现 追到4比4
双方各自保发 第二盘进入抢七
Top ten tennis right there.
这就是世界前十的水准
It's great work from Svitolina.
斯维托丽娜打得太出色了
抢七6比5
郑钦文的第一个赛点被救回
6比6 这一分
她再次用长回合争到机会
Oh, what a point!
噢 多精彩的一分
And it's won by Zheng.
郑钦文拿下了这一分
And it's a belated birthday gift for Zheng Qinwen,
这是送给郑钦文的迟到生日礼物
and she cannot believe it.
她自己都难以相信
Onto the ground she goes.
她倒在了球场上
And her coaches are enjoying that.
她的教练们也为此欣喜
Look at Pere Riba. He's loving it.
看看佩雷 里巴 他太开心了
The crowd going wild in Beijing.
北京的现场观众沸腾了
A belated birthday present.
一份迟到的生日礼物
Turned 24 years old yesterday.
她昨天刚满24岁
And Zheng Qinwen in front of her home crowd
郑钦文在主场观众面前
into the semifinals of the China Open.
打进了中国网球公开赛半决赛
Six three, seven six.
比分6比3 7比6
What a win. What a moment.
多么精彩的胜利 多么动人的时刻
Second time that she's been
这是她第二次
in the semifinals here in Beijing.
打进北京站半决赛
整场 郑钦文一发得分率 75%
11次破发机会 抓住4次
领先被追回 她又抓住机会
第二次来到中网半决赛
郑钦文下一轮对阵梅尔滕斯
生日之后 她还能再进一轮吗？